睡梦医生
你去哪  薇奥莱特[意为紫罗兰]
Where you going, Violet?
去采些花儿
Just to pick some flowers.
别走远了
Don't wander too far.
佛罗里达州
1980年
♪ 我的爱尔兰野玫瑰 ♪
♪ My wild Irish rose ♪
♪ 是最甜美的花朵 ♪
♪ The sweetest flower that grows ♪
♪ 任你遍寻世间 ♪
♪ You may search everywhere ♪
♪ 也没什么能和我的爱尔兰野玫瑰媲美 ♪
♪ But none can compare with my wild Irish rose ♪
你好啊
Well, hi there.
你是在哪找到那些的
Where did you find those?
我知道所有的秘密地点
I know all the secret places.
你想要一朵吗
Do you want one?
你在想我为何戴着这顶可笑的帽子
You're wondering why I'm wearing such a funny hat.
我一直戴着它
I always wear this hat.
经常戴  它都成我名字的一部分了
So much, it's a part of my name now.
我的朋友们...
My friends...
非常非常好的朋友  他们喊我帽子萝西
my very, very best friends, they just call me Rose the Hat.
看着像是魔法师的帽子
It looks like a magician's hat.
确实是
It is.
这是顶魔法帽子
It's a magic hat.
你想看看吗
Do you wanna see?
我手上没东西
Nothing up my sleeves.
帽子里也没东西
Nothing in my hat.
别害怕  那是我朋友
Don't worry, that's my friend.
你要错过戏法了
You're missing the trick.
把手伸进去
Reach inside.
-太漂亮了  -因为它很特别
- It's so pretty. - Because it's special.
说到特别
And speaking of special,
你也是个小魔法师  是不是
you're a little magic, too, aren't you?
我手里的花  是什么颜色的
The flower in my hand, what color is it?
没事的  宝贝
Oh, it's okay, honey.
我不会被吓到的  我保证
You won't scare me. I promise.
紫色的
Purple.
紫罗兰
Violet...
和你一样
like you.
花不能吃的
You don't eat flowers.
可以吃
But you do.
但这些花很特别
But these are special.
宝贝  特别的才最好吃
Honey, it's the special ones that taste best.
我该回去找我妈妈了
I should get back to my mom.
别走  再待一会儿
No, stay. Stay awhile.
多看点魔术
See more magic.
你是个特别的小东西  是不是
You are a special little thing, aren't you?
薇奥莱特
Violet?
Violet!
薇奥莱特
薇...
Vi...
第一章
旧日的鬼魂
丹尼
求你了
Please.
没事了  医生
Hey. It's okay, Doc.
没事了
It's okay.
好了
There.
干干爽爽
All dry.
发生什么事了
What happened?
你得和我说话啊  丹尼
You have to talk to me, Danny.
你回来后一直没说话  自从...
You haven't talked since we left...
拜托了  医生
Please, Doc.
求你了
Please.
所以说...
So...
你不说话是吧  医生
you ain't talking, huh, Doc?
我第一次见你时你也不怎么说话
Weren't talking much first time I met you neither.
小男孩一个
Little boy...
不得不在那个可怕的地方度过漫长的冬天
set to spend a long winter at that rotten old place.
只有他和他爸爸妈妈
Just him and his mommy and daddy.
爸爸有多黑暗  小男孩就有多光明
Daddy as dark as that boy is bright.
那个小男孩可明亮了
And, boy, is he bright.
他的闪灵像团火一样发着光
He's shining like fire...
然而那个地方
in the one place...
对于有闪灵能力的人而言是最不好的
the worst place for someone who shines.
你还记得我们第一次真正的交流吗
You remember the first time we really talked?
我在你脑子里说话的那次
When I spoke up inside your head?
那次让你感觉很好  是吧
Made you feel good, right?
得知自己并不孤独
Knowing you weren't alone.
爸爸想杀了我
Daddy tried to kill me.
他那时已经不是他了  你得理解
It wasn't all him, you gotta know.
那个地方供养了他的黑暗  蚕食了你的光明
That place fed his dark, like it fed on your light.
他内心也是有光明的
And he had some light in him, too.
就和你内心也是有黑暗的一样
Just like you got some dark.
我们都是既光明又黑暗
We all got both.
它还没有放过我
It's not done with me.
你有没有想过我每次都是怎样出现的
It ever strike you funny how I showed up when I did?
每当你需要我的时候
When you needed me.
有人也这样帮助过我
Someone did that for me, too.
我奶奶教我的
My grandma taught me,
而我教给了你
and I taught you.
有朝一日  丹尼·托伦斯
And some day, Danny Torrance,
你也会教给别人
you'll teach someone else.
我不会的
I won't.
你不会是吗
Oh, you won't, huh?
我是说我不会再用闪灵了
I won't shine, I mean.
不会了  太危险了
No more. It's dangerous.
我猜有时候是的
Reckon it is sometimes.
她找到我了
She found me.
她会不断来找我  直到她抓到我
She'll come back and come back until she gets me.
你说得对
You're right.
眺望酒店已经荒废了  被封起来了
The Overlook's condemned. Boarded up.
那些饥饿的老鬼魂
They're starvin' old ghosts,
他们在到处找你
and they're reachin' out for you.
不会只有她一个的
Won't stop with her, either.
书里的插画
Pictures in a book.
你说过他们只是书里的插画
You said they were just pictures in a book
他们伤害不了我
and they couldn't hurt me.
对于一些东西而言
Some things,
一些黑暗的东西  闪灵如同食物
dark things, the shining's like food.
他们就是闻到腥味的苍蝇
They're mosquitoes landing for blood.
眺望酒店
The Overlook,
对于我而言它向来都只是插画
it was always just pictures to me.
但我的闪灵能力没你强
But I didn't shine like you.
没有人的闪灵能力有你强
Nobody shines like you.
所以你在那个破酒店里
So, you in that damn hotel,
就像是个百万伏的电池
you was like a million-watt battery all plugged in.
酒店被充了电
And it ate it up.
你让它变成了真的
You made it real.
你踏进酒店门的那一刻就开始了
Started soon as you walked through the door.
我们对此无能为力  很抱歉告诉你这点
Can't do nothing about that, I'm sorry to tell you,
但你已经不是小孩子了
but you're not a child.
你已经长大了
You're older now.
从某种程度上讲  成熟了不少
Much older, in a way.
你必须听好了
You gotta hear this.
这是个饥肠辘辘的世界
World's a hungry place.
最黑暗的东西也是最饥饿的
And the darkest things are the hungriest,
他们会蚕食一切发光的东西
and they'll eat what shines.
他们就像蚊子蚂蝗一样成群结队
Swarm it like mosquitoes or leeches.
人们对此无能为力
Can't do nothing about that.
而你能做的
What you can do...
就是用他们渴求的东西来对付他们
is turn what they come for against 'em.
我爷爷
My grandfather,
他是个刻薄的老混蛋
he was a mean son of a bitch.
内心很黑暗
Dark inside.
和你爸爸一样的黑暗
Same type of dark as your dad.
他曾把我和我奶奶打到不省人事
Beat me senseless, and my grandma, too,
他死的时候  我开心得手舞足蹈
and when he died, I danced.
但他不断地回来
But he kept on coming back.
站在我房间里
Standing in my room.
穿得灰不溜秋的
Suit all gray
浑身都是棺材里他身上长的霉散发的恶臭
and stinkin' from whatever mold was growin' on him in that box.
有一天  他抓住了我  他成了真的
One day, he grabbed me, and he was real.
他的指甲很长
His nails were long
是在坟墓里长的
from growing in the grave,
他抓伤了我  医生
and they cut me, Doc.
很深的口子
Cut me deep.
我奶奶
So, Grandma,
她教了我一个办法
she taught me a trick.
给了我一个礼物
Gave me a present.
我希望你好好熟悉这个盒子
I want you to know this box...
里里外外
inside and out.
别光是看  摸摸它
Don't just look at it. Touch it.
把鼻子探进去  闻闻有没有味道
Stick your nose inside and see if there's a smell.
熟悉每一个角落
Know every corner,
每一个细节
every single thing.
为什么
Why?
因为你要在脑袋里造一个一模一样的盒子
Because you're gonna build one just like it in your mind.
一个甚至更加特别的
One even more special.
等下次那个贱人再出现时
So next time that bitch comes around,
你就准备好了
you'll be ready.
你快回妈妈那儿去吧
Let's get you back to Mama.
温蒂会担心的
Wendy'll worry,
这辈子都不该再让她担心了
and she shouldn't have to worry another day in her life.
那位女士已经还清她的债了
That woman's paid her debt.
丹尼
Danny!
你在这里
There you are.
你跑哪去了
Where did you go, huh?
你快把我吓死了
You scared me half to death.
不许这样吓我了  听见了吗
Don't you do that to me. You hear?
再也不许这样了
Don't you ever do that to me.
失踪儿童
薇奥莱特·汉森
再也不许了
Don't ever do that to me.
怎么了  医生
What's up, Doc?
干什么呢
What's the bit?
在煮什么呢
What's cookin'?
在煮什么  小朋友  在煮你呀
What's cooking, little friend? Why, you are.
我
Me?
没错
Why, yes.
烫死我了
You're killing me!
我看看
Let me see now.
显然这不是普通兔子
It is obvious that this is no ordinary rabbit.
因此  我必须想出一个绝妙的大师级的策略
Therefore, I must dream up a brilliant master strategy,
非常巧妙的
ingenious...
你没事吧  医生
You okay, Doc?
如果我把他引到
Now, uh, what if I lured him...
-嗯  我没事  -碎石机里呢
- Yeah, Mom. I'm okay. - ...into a rock crusher?
不不不  太复杂了
Nah, nah, nah, too complicated.
是的是的  太复杂了  但如果我
Yeah, yeah, too complicated. But what if I...
太多细节
Too much detail.
是的  太多细节了
Right. Too much detail.
你叫什么来着  帅哥
And what's your name again, cutie?
丹
Dan.
新泽西州
2011年
我刚刚正和这位美女喝酒呢
I was having a drink with the lady, all right?
你该吃药了
You're gonna take your medicine.
放开他
Get off him.
起来  滚出去
Get up. Get out of here.
靠  我觉得你把他打死了
Shit. I think you killed him.
如果你把他打死了怎么办
What if you killed him?
我希望你把他打死了
I hope you killed him.
听见了吗
You hear me?
亲一下就好了
Let me kiss it better.
不
No.
不不不
No, no, no.
不不不不不不
No, no, no, no, no, no.
怎么...不
What the... No.
粮票
妈妈
Mommy?
你叫什么名字  小英雄
What's your name, hero?
-妈妈  -宝宝
- Mommy? - Baby.
来  来
Here, here.
你可以把她的钱放回去  医生
You can put her money back, Doc.
这是最起码的
You can do that much.
她拿走了我的
She took mine.
八成是拿去买可卡因了
She probably bought the coke with it.
医生
Doc.
不不  医生
No, no, Doc.
你可以把眺望酒店的东西锁进盒子里
You can put things from the Overlook away in boxes,
而不是把回忆锁进去
but not memories.
千万不要这么做
Never those.
那些是真实的鬼魂
They're the real ghosts.
你要背负着它们
You take them with you.
新罕布什尔州  安尼斯顿
该睡觉啦  阿布拉
Time for bed, Abra.
再弹一会儿
A little more.
不行  宝贝
No more, sweetie.
明天是个大日子
Big day tomorrow.
生日派对
Birthday party!
-没错  -对
- That's right. - Yeah.
现在该干什么了
Now, what time is it?
-睡觉  -你知道现在该睡觉了
- Bedtime. - You know it's bedtime.
晚安  宝贝
Good night, sweetheart.
As Time Goes By - Dooley Wilson
电影《卡萨布兰卡》主题曲
♪ It's still The same old story ♪
纽约  长岛
♪ A fight for love and glory ♪
♪ A case of do or die ♪
♪ The world will always Welcome lovers ♪
♪ As time goes by ♪
亨利说喝完这瓶还要再来三瓶
Henri wants us to finish this bottle and then three more.
安蒂
Andi?
说他宁可用香槟去浇花园
Says he'll water his garden with champagne...
是我
That's right.
也不能留给德国人喝
before he'll let the Germans drink it.
你比照片上漂亮
You're prettier than your picture.
而你比照片上老
And you're older than yours.
我们要待在这里还是去别的地方
Are we staying here or going somewhere?
你不想看电影吗
Don't you wanna watch the movie?
我不明白有什么好大惊小怪的
I don't see what the fuss is about.
聊天室的恋情而已
Chat room romance.
有点恶心  一点也没意思
Little gross. Not interesting.
看就是了  很有意思的  我保证
Just watch. It's interesting, I promise.
最好真的有意思  她的灵气可不算多强
Well, it better be, 'cause she's not all that steamy.
开始了
And there she goes.
你不累吗
Aren't you tired?
睡吧
Sleep.
好吧
Okay.
等着  这才是最精彩的部分
Wait. This is the best part.
我已经看她做过三次了  百看不厌
I watched her do it three times now and it never gets old.
睡得再沉一些
Sleep deeper,
越沉越好
deep as you can.
你感受到的疼痛只是一场梦
The pain you feel is only a dream.
疼痛是什么
What will the pain be?
一场梦
A dream.
要是你老婆问起
You can explain a lost wallet
钱包丢了你可以解释
when your wife asks.
但这你可解释不了
But you can't explain this.
以后你每天照镜子都会看到它
This you'll see every day when you look in the mirror.
而你每次看到
And every time you see it,
都要大声说
you'll say out loud...
"我喜欢小姑娘"
"I like little girls."
你要大声说出来
You'll say it out loud.
大声说出来
Out loud.
下次你去网上找小姑娘时
And the next time you go looking for a little girl online,
我要你想起
I want you to remember that time
你被蛇咬的那一次
you got bit by a snake.
一条穿着白色上衣的蛇
A snake in a white blouse
面孔却是一片空白
whose face is a blank.
还真有意思
That is interesting.
正在放映  《卡萨布兰卡》
稍等  女士
Excuse me, miss?
女士  你落了东西在影院里
Miss. Miss, you left something in the theater.
你不想打扰我
You wanna leave me alone.
你好啊
Well, hi there.
你想放开我
You wanna let me go.
不  亲爱的
Oh, no, sweetie.
我不想
No, I don't.
我这些钱最远能去哪
How far can I get for this?
新罕布什尔州  弗雷泽
生日快乐  阿布拉
黑桃四  这是什么颜色
Four of spades. What color is this?
妈妈  我给你做了这个  这是张秘密卡片
Mommy, I made this for you. It's a secret card.
你好
谢谢  阿布宝贝
Thank you, Abba-doo.
有谁会什么咒语吗
Does anyone know a magic word?
你
You.
妈咪妈咪哄
Abracadabra.
非常棒
That's a great one.
好  你拿着魔杖
Okay, you hold the magic wand.
现在  所有人注意
Now, everyone,
我们数到三  好吗
on the count of three, okay?
一  二  三
One, two, three.
妈咪妈咪哄
Abracadabra.
我也会魔法
I know magic, too.
那你可以抱着它  小寿星
Well, then you get to hold him, birthday girl.
来  抱住了吗
There you go. You got him?
我的下一个戏法...天啊  抱歉
For my next trick... Oh, my goodness. Sorry.
有时候我...
Sometimes, if I...
抱歉
Sorry.
有人看到我的勺子了吗
Has anyone seen my spoons?
这个我也会
I can do that.
那挺好  亲爱的
That's nice, sweetie.
-就在你身上  -在我身上吗
- They're on you! - Oh, they're on me?
你们可千万不能这样
Okay, make sure you guys don't do this.
别想睡午觉了
We can forget about naptime.
再坚持几小时就好
Just a few more hours.
跟着我说  "再坚持几小时就好"
Say it with me. "Just a few more hours."
再坚持几小时就好
Just a few more hours.
什么鬼
What the hell?
戴夫
Dave...
妈咪妈咪哄
Abracadabra.
第二章
空洞的恶魔
你好啊  瞌睡虫
Well, hi there, sleepyhead.
抱歉
Sorry.
我不得不让你睡沉一点
I had to sleep you pretty hard.
你很难搞定
You're a tough one.
意志很强
Willful.
知道吗  我查了
You know, I checked.
三个月里有六个男人
Six men in three months
脸上被文了那种蛇咬文身
with those little snakebite tattoos on their cheeks.
你还真忙啊
Why, you've been busy.
蛇咬安蒂  原来就是你
Snakebite Andi, that's who you are.
那么  我是谁
So, who am I?
你是绑架了我的疯婆子
You're some crazy bitch who kidnapped me.
现在开始只说实话
Just the truth from now on.
你将只说实话
You will only speak the truth.
你是我见过的最美的女人
You're the most beautiful woman I've ever seen.
天  效果也太好了点  是吧
My God. Works a little too well, don't it?
听好了  蛇咬安蒂
Here's the deal, Snakebite Andi.
你是个说服者  对吧  你可以说服人们
You're a pusher, hmm? You can push people.
我们有一阵子没有说服者了
We haven't had a pusher around here for a little while,
所以我要给你开一个条件
so I'm gonna offer you a deal
这条件我快四十年没给人开过了
I haven't offered anyone in almost 40 years.
你多大了  亲爱的
How old are you, darlin'?
十五岁
Fifteen.
Fifteen?
天  多好的年纪啊
Oh, God, what an age.
正是含苞待放的时候  是吧
Springtime of your womanhood, isn't it?
你已经不是小女孩了
You're not a girl anymore,
但你也还没有一点岁月的痕迹
but you don't have a single dent yet either.
地心引力甚至都没注意到你
Gravity hasn't even noticed you.
十五岁的时候不会
Not at 15.
不过男人嘛
Men, though...
不不不  不用害羞
No, no, no. No shame.
你通通还回去了  对吧
You paid that back, didn't you?
这就是我要提供给你的  青春永驻
That's what I'm offering you. Springtime forever.
从现在起十年后  你还是十五岁
Ten years from now, you're still 15.
一百年后  可能十七岁
A hundred, maybe 17.
吃得好
Eat well,
永葆青春  长生不老
stay young, live long.
所以你和你朋友...
So, you and your friend...
不是我的朋友  那是我的家人
Not my friend. That's my family.
我们是真结族  亲爱的
We're the True Knot, dear.
真结族
The True Knot.
绑定之物无法解绑
What's tied can never be untied.
新罕布什尔州  弗雷泽
城市药房  肥皂盒专卖店
你喜欢吗
You like it?
抱歉  我只是...
Sorry. I was just...
没关系  人们总喜欢凑近了看
That's okay. People love to look at it.
我们以前都是在图书馆里布置这些的
We used to set this up in the library.
社区项目  仿佛自己活过来了
Community project, just taking a life all its own.
看  我们是从那边的钟楼开始的
See, we started with the clock tower there.
-是吗  -越建越多
- Oh, yeah. - Just keeps growing.
孩子们叫它迷你镇
Kids call it Teenytown.
这是孩子们建的
The kids build this?
在一些帮助之下  是的
With some help, oh, yeah.
继续下去就能建好整个城镇广场
Keep it up, build the whole town square.
你是坐大巴来的还是搭的顺风车
Are you off the bus or riding your thumb?
大巴
Yeah, the bus.
很少有人会坐大巴来这么北部的地方
Not many ride the bus this far north.
除非是想找工作
Unless they're looking for work.
嗯
Yeah.
是想换个环境
Change of scenery,
还是在逃离什么
or you running away from something?
别介意  希望我没有...
Don't mind me. I hope I'm...
只是想跟新面孔聊聊
New face is all.
嗯
Yeah.
我想我是在逃离自己吧
Guess I'm running away from myself, I guess.
是吗
Oh, yeah.
我认识这种表情  恐怕是太熟悉了
I know that look. Too well, I'm sorry to say.
逃离自己  这可不好办
Running away from yourself. That is a pickle.
你不管去哪都得带着自己
You take yourself with you wherever you go.
很操蛋吧
Ain't that the bitch?
租金85一周
Rent's 85 a week,
要先付钱
payable up front.
比利帮你付了头两周的钱  其余的你得自己交
Billy paid your first two, rest's on you.
不能养宠物  不能办派对  不能吵闹
No pets, no parties, no noise.
我是个安静的租客
I'm a quiet tenant.
上一个人也是这么说的  学数学的学生
Last guy said the same. Math student.
我甚至让他把墙刷成了黑板
Even let him paint the wall all blackboard,
好让他在上面演算他的谜题
so he could scribble his little puzzles up there.
根本不安静  一点都不
Wasn't quiet. No, sir.
走的时候都没给我刷回原样  不过幸好没刷
Didn't even paint over this when he left, but I'm glad he didn't,
这样就能让你轻松记住了
'cause I can make this easy for ya,
你每天醒来都会看到它
so you see it every morning when you wake.
85一周
老实点
你确定要帮这小子做担保吗
You sure you wanna vouch for this pup?
非常确定
Pretty sure.
倒霉的是你  比利
It's your ass, Billy.
这家伙就是心太软
Bleedin' heart, this one.
我在楼下  一楼  有需要可以找我
I'm downstairs, ground floor, if you need anything.
明天来找我  聊聊工作的事
Find me tomorrow, talk about some work.
你为什么要做这些
Why are you doing this?
你都不认识我
You don't know me.
是的
No, I don't.
但我认识你那表情  我之前说过了
But I know the look, like I said.
有时候我对人会有种第六感
And sometimes I get this feeling about people.
可能很难理解
Hard to understand, I guess.
没你想的那么难
Easier than you think.
-谢了  -没事
- Thanks. - All right.
准备好了吗
You ready?
她准备好了
She's ready.
这些人是谁
Who... Who are these people?
你一会就知道了
You'll find out after.
那边那个是弗力克大爷
That over there is Grampa Flick...
他会引导我们  躺下
and he'll lead us. Lie down.
来
There.
不要害怕  明白吗
No fear. You understand?
我们是真结族
We are the True Knot
我们生生不息
and we endure.
我们是天选之子
We are the chosen ones.
我们是幸运之人
We are the fortunate ones.
绑定之物无法解绑
What is tied cannot be untied.
这里有一个女人
Here is a woman.
她会加入我们吗
Would she join us?
她会把自己的命与我们绑定吗
Would she tie her life to our life?
是的
Yes.
说是的
Say yes.
是的
Yes.
这个很特别
This one's special.
她叫维奥莱特
Her name's Violet.
她已经所剩无几了
There's not much of her left.
而她的味道
And she tastes...
如同花朵
like flowers.
深吸气
Breathe deep.
对  接受它
There. Embrace it.
接受它
Embrace it.
不
No!
不  不
No! No!
他们还没找到我们
They haven't found us yet.
他们听惯了他的哭声
They were used to hearing him cry
因为我总是扔下他一个人
'cause I left him alone so much.
所以他们无动于衷
So they didn't do anything.
他们还没发现我们
And they haven't found us yet.
妈妈
Mommy?
你说你认识我的表情
Uh, you said that you knew my look.
是什么意思
Well, what did you mean?
兄弟
Brother...
你病了
you're sick.
你很累  我看得出来
You're tired. I can see that much.
但是你又十分厌倦这种状态
But you're sick and tired of being sick and tired.
我需要帮助
I need help.
进来吧
Come on in.
我们聊聊
We'll talk about it.
上帝  请赐予我平静的心去接受我无法改变的
God, grant me the serenity to accept the things I cannot change,
赐予我勇气去改变我能改变的事情
the courage to change the things I can,
赐予我智慧去分辨两者
and the wisdom to know the difference.
博比今天过生日
Well, Bobbie's got a big birthday today.
三年整  戒酒三年
Three years. Three years sober.
棒
Yeah.
我太为你骄傲了
I'm so proud of you.
谢谢  约翰
Thanks, John.
我忘记谁了吗
Now, am I forgetting anybody?
有没有一年整的  或者半年的
Does anybody got a year? Or six months?
现在轮到屋子里最重要的人了
Well, now for the most important person in the room.
有新来的吗
Is, uh, anybody here a newbie?
有人戒酒24小时了吗
Somebody got 24 hours?
有
Yeah.
新搬来的
New to town, huh?
是的  我...
Yeah, I, uh...
没别的意思  这屋子里有一半人是我接生的
Nothing personal. I delivered half the people in the room.
-只是看到了新面孔而已  -这位是丹·托伦斯
- Just new faces pop, that's all. - This here is Dan Torrance.
刚乘大巴来的
He's fresh off the bus.
看样子也刚摔了一跤
Fresh off the ground, by the look.
这里不会评头论足  兄弟
There's no judgment here, brother.
我们都经历过
I mean, we've all been there.
-经历过更惨的  相信我  -是的
- And worse, trust me. - Oh, yeah.
这位医生  我记事起他就在我们镇上工作
Doc, he's served our town most my life.
-我弟弟就是他接生的  -是的
- Delivered my baby brother. - Yeah.
弗兰基最近怎么样
How is Frankie these days?
他会迷途知返的
Well, he'll find his way back.
他内心深处是个好人
You know, he's got a good heart under it all.
比利真的尽力帮他了  我们都尽力了
Billy really tried with him. Well, we all did.
比利  要知道
Well, Billy, you know,
如果你需要一个可以避风的港湾
if you're looking for a wing to climb under...
绝对找不到比比利·弗里曼更靠谱的了
I can't say you'll do any better than Billy Freeman here.
谢谢你的热情招待
Thank you for your hospitality. I...
我有点
I'm a little, uh...
我可能还是不习惯
I guess I'm not used to it.
你知道有句话
Well, you know we say,
"不了解来龙去脉  就不能妄加评判别人"
"You can't judge someone till you know their whole story."
你可能觉得自己明白
You might think you understand,
-但其实不明白  -不明白
- but you don't. - You don't.
你今天过得怎么样  还好吗
So, how are you today? All right?
小火车还在开
Train's still running.
那挺好的
That's good to hear.
你没事吧
You good?
没事  没事
Yeah. Yeah.
很高兴认识你  丹
Well, good to know you, Dan.
-我也是  -有空再来
- Yeah. - Come again.
-谢谢  -希望很快能再见面
- Thanks. - Hope to see you again soon.
我会再来的
I'll... I'll come back, yeah.
人特别好  他很有天赋
Really good man. He's got a gift...
是  比利  等下
Yeah. Hey, Billy, hang on.
医生
Hey, Doc.
你的手表
Your watch.
你的手表丢了  你当时担心那个孩子  得了
You lost your watch. You were worried about the kid with, uh...
古雪氏
Goocher's.
什么
What?
得了古氏或者高氏的那个孩子  骨头的病
The kid with Goocher's or Gaucher's. The bone thing.
高雪氏症
Gaucher's disease.
对
Right.
你在医院的洗手间洗手
You were washing your hands in the hospital bathroom
你把它放在洗手液旁边了
and you left it on the soap dispenser.
去看看洗手液旁边就行了
Just check on the soap dispenser.
-很高兴认识你  -好
- It's good to meet you. - Yeah.
你是怎么知道的
How did you know?
约翰·道尔顿医生
我也希望能说清楚
I wish I could say.
碰巧猜到的
Lucky guess.
瞎说
My ass.
应该是直觉  直觉告诉我的
Intuition, I suppose. Like a feeling in my gut. Maybe a...
碰巧猜中了
A lucky guess.
你想在这里做什么
What do you wanna do here?
什么意思
What do you mean?
我是说在弗雷泽  你为什么来这里
I mean here in Frazier. Why are you here?
别跟我说套话  丹
And don't bullshit me, Dan.
我更相信自己的直觉
I'm prone to gut feelings of my own.
我不知道  我也说不好
I don't know. I don't know.
做些跟我以前做的不一样的事
Something different than I've been doing.
好一点的事
Something better.
老实说  做什么都比以前好
Anything's better, frankly.
你做礼拜吗
You go to church?
重要吗
Does it matter?
你有信仰吗  比你
Do you believe in something? Something...
更宏大的东西
bigger than you?
信仰不能让我们成为更好的人
Our... Our beliefs don't make us better people.
行动才能让我们成为更好的人
Our actions make us better people.
比利说  你有过做护工的经验
So, Billy says you have orderly experience.
是的
That's right.
你现在有工作吗
You workin' right now?
在迷你镇做零工 帮忙看小火车
A few shifts at Teenytown. Helping with the train.
我每周在利文顿临终安养院工作三天
'Cause I do three days a week at Rivington House, the hospice.
好的护工很难找
Good orderly is tough to find.
留住更难
Tougher to keep.
你害怕垂死的人吗
Do dying people bother you?
不怕
No.
我们都会死
We're all dying.
这世界就是个空气清新的大型安养院
The world is one big hospice with fresh air.
你好啊
Well, hi there.
-我睡了多久...  -几天
- How long was I... - Oh, few days.
你说不会疼的
You said it didn't hurt.
现在不疼了  对吧
Doesn't now, does it?
当时感觉我要死了
Felt like I was dying.
我知道
I know.
你确实死了
You did.
你把我复活了
You brought me back.
等你吃了东西就会好受些
You'll feel better when you eat.
我还是人类吗
Am I still human?
你在乎吗
Do you care?
It's All Forgotten Now - Ray Noble and His Orchestra
♪ It's all forgotten now ♪
♪ The trouble and the pain ♪
♪ Forgotten, Every word I said ♪
♪ Every tear you shed ♪
♪ We're still in love ♪
好了
There you go.
怎么了
What is it?
你怕我
You're scared of me.
我们爱你胜过世界上的一切
We love you more than anything in the world.
明白吗
You hear me?
胜过一切
Anything.
晚安  亲爱的
Goodnight, my heart.
别去烦他
Let him be.
阿兹里  别烦他
Azreel, leave him be.
阿兹
Azzie?
阿兹  过来
Azzie, come on.
过来  阿兹
Come on. Azzie.
医生
Doc.
是你吗  医生
That you, Doc?
不  我不是医生
No, I'm not a doctor.
需要我帮你叫医生过来吗
Do you want me to get you a doctor?
猫到我的床上来了
The cat's on my bed.
我把它弄走
I'll move her.
不
No.
我知道它会来
I knew she would be.
这只猫似乎一直都知道
That cat always seems to know...
大限是什么时候
when it's time.
-我猜大限到了  -不
- I guess it's time. - No.
阿兹就是一只傻乎乎的猫
It's just Azzie being a silly old cat.
不
Nope.
自从我来到这里就一直这样
Been that way ever since I got here.
这只猫知道
The cat knows
什么时候该长睡不醒了
when it's time to go to sleep.
大家都知道
Everybody knows that.
我要死了
I'm gonna die.
是的
Yes.
我帮你叫人来
Let me get you someone.
不
No.
知道大限到了
Known it was comin'.
不代表就不感到害怕了
Doesn't make it less scary.
是的
Yeah.
但也许就像你说的
But maybe it's just like you say,
只是睡过去了
just going to sleep.
没什么好怕的  只是睡着了
I mean, there's nothing scary. It's just sleeping.
你真是奇怪的医生
You're a strange type of doctor.
-我说过了  我不是医生  -我觉得你是
- I told you, I'm not a doctor. - Oh, I think you are.
睡梦医生
Doctor Sleep.
医生  我怕会疼  会很黑
Doc, I am so scared it's gonna hurt, or be dark,
或者会化为虚无  我不想...
or... or be nothing at all. And I don't wanna...
没什么好怕的
Nothing to be scared of.
只是睡着而已
Just going to sleep.
终于能真正安宁地睡着
Finally, true, restful sleep.
谢谢
Oh, thank you.
谢谢你  医生
Thank you, Doc.
我不应该在这里  我去帮你叫...
Look, I shouldn't be here. Let me go get you some...
不  不用
No, no, no.
你恰恰应该在这里
You're exactly where you should be.
就在这里
Exactly.
我看见我的妻子了
I see my wife.
你好
第三章
小间谍
我是丹  我酗酒
Dan, alcoholic.
八年后
你好  丹
Hi, Dan.
我不是一个善于言辞的人
I'm not much of a speech guy.
我觉得我应该握着这个纪念章
I just thought I'd hold the chip and
想到什么说什么
talk about whatever popped up.
我站在了这里
So, here I am.
我想到了我爸
And I'm thinkin' about my dad.
我有一次见过他手里拿着这样的纪念章
I saw a chip like this in his hand once.
就在他去世前的几个月
A couple months before he died.
五个月纪念章  我很确定
Five month chip, I'm pretty sure.
有一次他喝醉后伤害了我
He hurt me once when he was drunk.
弄断了我的胳膊
Broke my arm.
然后他就戒酒了
Then he dried right out.
我五岁时他去世了  所以我了解他的唯一方式
He died when I was five, so the only way I got to know him,
真正了解他的方式  就在我堕落的时候
really got to know him, was when I went dark.
我喝得天昏地暗的时候
When I... When I drank to dull the...
或者
or, uh...
我想要暴打别人的时候
whenever I wanted to break someone's face,
因为喝酒  发脾气以及愤怒
'cause the drinking and the temper and the anger,
都是他遗传给我的
those things in me were his.
这些是我对他的全部了解
And they were all I could know of him.
但是现在  我对他的了解有所不同
But now, well, now I get to know him a little different...
因为他也曾站在这样的一个房间里
'cause he also stood in a room like this once...
希望为了我和我妈好起来
wanting to get well for me and my mom.
他手里握着这样的纪念章
And he held the chip in his hand
上面写着五个月
and the chip said five months,
在那天  他...
and on that day, he...
在一切发生之前
Before it all...
那天  他最大的愿望
Well, on that day, all he wanted in the world
就是站在我今天所站的位置
was to stand where I'm standing now.
而我做到了  所以
And here I am, so
谢谢大家给我们两个的机会
thank you for us both, I guess.
这个也是杰克·托伦斯的
This is for Jack Torrance.
查理
Hey, Charlie.
医生
Doc?
看来我不需要问你为什么这个时候来
Guess I don't need to ask why you're here at this hour.
你疼吗
Do you have pain?
要我去找克劳戴特给你拿药吗
Do you want me to get Claudette to bring you a pill?
药没用了
Pill won't matter.
我听说过你的上门服务
I heard about these house calls.
睡梦医生来拜访的真实原因
What a visit from Doctor Sleep really is.
你都看到了什么  医生
So, what do you see, Doc?
我看到了你的双胞胎儿子
I see your twin sons.
四岁
Four years old.
你能看到他们吗
Can you see them?
能
I do.
法尔毛拖拉机
Farmall tractor.
座位上有一把条纹雨伞
A striped umbrella over the seat.
五岁
Five years old,
拉着红色的小车
pulling a red wagon.
主啊  快瞧瞧
Lord, look at that.
就像一副纸牌
Like a deck of cards.
全部按序排列
All out of order.
我并不害怕地狱  医生
I'm not scared of hell, Doc.
我度过了体面的一生
Uh, I lived a decent life.
再说我觉得并没有地狱
I don't think there is such a place anyway.
我猜我只是害怕
I guess I'm scared...
化为虚无
there's nothing.
从虚无中出生
There was nothing before.
万一  死后也是虚无呢
So, what if there's nothing after?
生命没有终点  查理
We don't end, Charlie.
我非常确定
I know that for certain.
其他的东西我了解不多  但是
I don't know much else... but
我知道生命没有终点
I know that we don't end.
蓝莓
Blueberries.
我能尝到我妈妈从前种的蓝莓
I can taste blueberries my mother used to grow.
你能尝到吗
Can you taste them?
我尝到了
Yeah, I can.
我还能听到你那台老收音机里放着法兰克的歌
And I can hear Frank on your old radio.
你总是把它放在工具台上  摆在工具旁边
The one you used to have on your workbench next to your tools.
♪ 和我一起翱翔 ♪
♪ Come fly with me ♪
♪ 一起翱翔  飞到远方 ♪
♪ Let's fly, let's fly away ♪
♪ 如果想要喝到异域的琼浆 ♪
♪ If you can use Some exotic booze ♪
♪ 在遥远的孟买有一家酒吧 ♪
♪ There's a bar in far Bombay ♪
♪ 和我一起翱翔 ♪
♪ Come fly with me ♪
♪ 一起翱翔 ♪
♪ Let's fly, let's fly... ♪
♪ 飞到远方 ♪
♪ Away ♪
早上好
好久不见  笔友
Been a minute, little pen pal.
上学
阿布拉  该上学了
Abra? School.
好  我知道
Fine, I know.
大爷  看到萝西了吗
Hey, Gramps, you seen Rosie?
瞭望塔
Watchtower.
你还好吗
You feelin' okay?
好得不得了
Peachy keen.
抱歉打扰你了
Sorry to interrupt.
有收获吗
Any luck?
快了
Gettin' closer.
我觉得他应该在爱荷华
He's somewhere in Iowa, I think.
找到他后  我们就要开始长途公路旅行
We'll all take a nice long road trip once I'm sure I've found him.
在我找到他之前  我们
Until I do, we...
你得开一个罐子  萝西
You gotta open a canister, Rosie.
我们六个月前吸过灵气  乌鸦
We took steam six months ago, Crow.
六个月算不了什么
Six months is nothing.
特拉华州那孩子灵气不够强
That kid in Delaware wasn't so steamy
而且已经开始显现了
and it's already showing.
你看到弗力克大爷的头发了吗
You see Grampa Flick's hair, yeah?
看到了
Yeah.
我觉得他状态不太好
I don't think he's well.
尼克松执政的时候弗力克大爷就不太好了
Grampa Flick hasn't been well since Nixon was in office.
我知道
I know.
但是我们需要进食  所有人都需要
But we need to eat. All of us.
罐子不够了吗
Are the canisters low?
当然不是
'Course not.
马上就能猎杀了  没必要再浪费一个
Just no need to waste one if you're close to the kill.
萝西
Rosie.
我可能需要进食才能找到他
I might need it just to find him.
以前世界上的灵气比现在要多
There used to be more steam in the world, you know?
别傻了  得了吧
Oh, don't be daft. Come on.
正如凡人们说的
That's like when rubes say,
"五十年前  邻里之前友好得多"
"50 years ago, people used to be more neighborly."
但这是事实  萝西
But it's true, Rosie.
世界上的灵气越来越少  也越来越微弱
There's less steam out there, and it's weaker, too.
我不知道是因为他们的手机还是饮食
I don't know if it's their cell phones or diets
又或是电视剧什么的
or their Netflix or what,
我最近都感觉不到他们了
but I am not picking up many scents these days,
即使我能感受到  萝西  也没有那么...
and the ones that I do, Rosie, are just not that...
今晚我开一个罐子帮大家度过难关
I'll open a canister tonight to tide everyone over.
谢谢
Thank you.
-你知道吗  萝西  -知道什么
- You know it, Rosie. - I know what?
这就是你每天都到这上面来的原因
It's why you're up here every day.
无论你对大家怎么说  你每天都会上来
It's why you're always up here no matter what you tell the others.
这世界灵气不再充裕
The world's not as steamy
你在寻找一个灵气强大的人
and you are looking for a whale.
爱荷华州  阿代尔
你看那个孩子  十九号
Oh, watch this kid. Number 19.
那孩子是个天才
That kid is a natural.
他每次都能击中球
He hits the ball every time.
就像能看透投手的想法一样
Like he can read the pitcher's mind.
是吗
Is that right?
看见了吧  早晚有一天  会有球探
See? You watch, one of these days, one of those talent scouts
听说这个布莱德  你就等着瞧吧
is gonna get wind of Brad there. You watch.
你好啊  十九号
Hey, 19,
刚才看了你的比赛
just saw your game.
你已经可以参加职业联赛了
You are ready for the majors.
-打得真漂亮  -谢谢
- Well played. - Thanks.
你是要回家吗
Hey, you headin' home?
上车吗  我载你一程
You wanna hop in? I'll give you a ride.
不用  挺近的
No, it's real close.
不用了
I'm good.
没事的
It's okay.
我们是朋友  你想上车  我们带你回家
We're friends. You wanna hop in. We'll take you right home.
你可以带我回家
You can take me right home.
你相信我
You trust me.
我相信你
I trust you.
不不  求你了  不要
No! No, please! No!
不  求你们放了我
No! Please let me go.
我不会说出去的  求你们了
Please, I won't tell. Please. Please!
十九号
Number 19.
孩子  你很出色
Kid, you were good.
不
No!
求你们了  放我走吧
No, please let me go.
我不会说出去的  求你们了
I won't tell. I won't tell. Please.
没事的
It's okay.
求你们了
Please.
你要伤害我吗
Are you gonna hurt me?
是的
Yes.
不
No!
疼痛净化灵气
Pain purifies steam.
恐惧亦然  请你理解
Fear, too, so, you understand.
住手
Stop!
Stop.
住手
Stop!
住手  怪物
Stop, monster.
住手  住手
Stop. Stop.
怎么了
What is it?
不  住手
No! Stop!
阿布拉  阿布拉
Abra! Abra!
宝贝  宝贝醒醒  快醒醒  宝贝
Sweetie. Sweetheart, wake up. Wake up, sweetheart.
阿布拉  醒醒
Abra, wake up!
-阿布拉  阿布拉  -快住手
- Abra! Abra! - Stop it!
天啊
Jesus.
红朗姆
谋杀
谁
好
Okay.
棒球男孩
该死  我以为他还能再撑几分钟
Damn. I thought he had another few minutes in him.
准备好了吗
Okay, ready?
他们杀了他
They killed him.
没事了
It's okay.
红朗姆
谋杀
谁
棒球男孩
刚刚有个窥视者
We had a looker.
今晚
Tonight?
对
Yeah.
灵气强吗
Big steam?
亲爱的  灵气极强
Oh, honey, it was huge.
在哪
Where?
应该是东海岸
East Coast, I think.
你是说有人在2400公里之外窥视了我们
You're saying someone looked in from 1,500 miles away?
也许更远
Maybe further.
男孩还是女孩
Boy or girl?
应该是女孩
Girl, I think.
她很快就离开了
She was out of there so fast.
但是我发誓  乌鸦老爹
But I swear, Crow Daddy,
我从没感受到过这样的力量
I haven't felt power like that,
这样原始的力量
raw power like that
太久没有过了
in so long.
那我们需要调查一下
Then we need to look into it.
-越快越好  -对
- Sooner the better. - Yeah.
万一吓到了她的父母
Case her parents freak out,
送她去精神病院
send her to a psychiatrist.
医院会她吃药  灵气就被毁了
You know, they get her on pills, could ruin the steam.
可能会抑制她...
Might muffle her just...
给这孩子吃帕罗西汀
No, giving Paxil to this kid,
就像是在探照灯上包上保鲜膜
it's like throwing a piece of Saran Wrap over a searchlight.
我不知道她在哪
I don't know where she is,
等她下次再来  她一定会再来的
but when she comes back, and she'll be back,
我会准备好的  亲爱的
oh, I'll be ready, honey.
我会准备好的
I'll be ready.
谋杀
谁
棒球男孩
希望你没事
你的朋友  丹
早上好
Morning.
你猜怎么着
Guess what.
我交到新朋友了
I made a new friend.
他叫丹
His name's Dan.
是吗  学校的吗
Yeah? At school?
不  他不住在这
No. He doesn't live here.
他住得很近
I mean, he lives close.
应该是在弗雷泽
Frazier, I think.
没什么大不了的
No big deal.
阿布  你还好吗
Abs, are you okay?
昨晚  我
Last night, I...
我没事
I'm okay.
昨晚的事很抱歉
Sorry about that.
我知道你的脑子有时候就像无线电
I know that head of yours is like a radio sometimes.
你会收听到一些奇怪的频道
And you pick up some weird stations.
没什么奇怪的
Nothing weird like that.
不会再发生了
Not anymore.
天呐
My God.
我得学习  不学习的话
I've gotta study. If I don't study...
跑阵  传给十一号然后
Running play. Hand-off to 11 and...
记不住的话教练会杀了我的
Coach is gonna kill me if I don't get these.
他为什么不喜欢我
Why doesn't he like me?
因为头发吗  我应该换个发型
My hair? I should change my hair.
那个怪胎又盯着我看了
The freak is staring at me again.
她看什么看
What is she staring at?
怪胎
Freak.
失踪儿童
布莱德利·特雷弗
阿布宝贝
Hey, Abba-doo.
爸爸
Hey, Dad.
学校怎么样
School okay?
书写得怎么样了
How's the book?
很好  进展很顺利
Good. Yeah, going good.
我在写查尔斯顿舞和黑臀舞
I'm writing about Charleston and Black Bottom.
就像
Yeah, it's...
-感觉就像  -我要去写作业了
- It's feeling like... - I'm going to start my homework.
好  好样的  宝贝
Okay. Good. That's good, sweetie.
三年后准备考哈佛吧
Think Harvard in three years.
到时候再说
We'll see.
好  到时候再说
Yeah. We will see.
失踪儿童
布莱德利·特雷弗
禁止非法闯入
坎顿治安部令
拉美克工业
乙醇工厂
东北入口
关停待通知
拉美克工业
乙醇工厂
东北入口
关停待通知
非常感谢您的光临
Thanks so much for shopping with us today.
我们总是为您提供新鲜的食材
And remember, we're always fresh, just for you.
你好啊
Well, hi there.
出去
Get out!
出去  从我脑子里出去
Get out! Get out of my head!
出去
Get out!
-女士  你还好吗  -别  别
- Ma'am, are you okay? - No! No.
我没事
Yeah, I'm fine.
I'm fine.
我的天
Jesus.
丹
Danno?
丹  丹
Dan? Dan?
起来  站起来  丹
Get up. Stand up, Dan.
起来  丹
Come on, Danno.
-怎么回事  -你突然就倒下了
- What happened? - Well, you just dropped.
还以为你中风了  托尼是谁
Thought you was having a stroke. Who's Tony?
什么
What?
你一直在说  "请帮帮我  托尼"
You kept saying, "Please help me, Tony."
我很抱歉
Well, I'm sorry about that.
萝西
Rosie?
我们有麻烦了
We've got a problem.
-跟我说说  -那个窥视者
- Talk to me. - The looker?
她又找到我了
Yeah, she found me again.
-怎么会  -我不知道
- How? - I don't know.
我不在乎
I don't care.
我们得抓到她  乌鸦  必须抓到
We have to have her, Crow. We have to.
她知道你是谁  我们在哪吗
Does she know who you are? Where we are?
不  我不知道  应该没有...
No, I don't know. I don't think...
那不重要  听着
That's not the important... Look.
-我说她的灵气很强  对吧  -嗯
- I said she's huge steam, right? - Mm-hmm.
事实上比那还强
Yeah, it's even bigger than that.
我试图在她脑中与她对抗
I tried to turn around in her
而她不费吹灰之力就把我赶了出来
and she blew me out of her like I was nothing.
-胡说吧  -不  我从未有过这种遭遇
- Bullshit. - No. Never happened to me, ever.
我以前会说这不可能
I would have said that was impossible.
我们是要吃了她  还是转化她
Is she food or do we turn her?
我们不转化她
We don't turn her.
萝西  你确定吗
Rosie, are you sure?
如果她真如你所说  那...
If she's what you say she is, then...
我们真结族里面不能允许有这种能力的人
Then we don't want anyone with that power in the Knot.
天啊  好好想想
Jeez. Think about it.
万一她都不是呢
What if she's neither?
什么意思
What do you mean?
我们不杀她
I mean, we don't kill her.
也不转化她
And we don't turn her.
想想如果是一头奶牛
Think of a cow.
杀了它  能吃一个月的肉
You butcher one, that gives you meat for a month.
让它活着
Keep it alive,
好好照顾
take care of it,
能喝几年的牛奶
it gives you milk for years.
-萝西  我们从没那么做过  -我知道
- Rosie, we've never tried that. - I know.
因为有灵气的头脑很危险
Because a steam head is dangerous.
让它活着  可能会有危险
You keep it alive, it could be dangerous.
我知道  重点...
I know. The point...
乌鸦  重点是
The point, Crow,
她就是我的大白鲸
is she's the great white whale.
我要她
And I want her.
I want her.
我他妈要她
I fucking want her.
第四章
转化  世界
祝你今天愉快
Have a great day.
你也是
You, too.
你好
Hi.
比利
Billy.
你能听到我的声音
You can hear me.
我们还是开口说话吧  好吗
Let's use our outside voices, all right?
你追踪到了我
You tracked me down?
比我想得容易  像我大脑中有导航系统一样
It was easier than I thought. Like GPS, but in my head.
听着  我无意冒犯  但在如今
Look, I don't mean any offense, but this day and age,
一个成年男子和一个小女孩坐在公园长椅上...
a grown man sitting with a teenage girl on a park bench...
我是阿布拉·斯通  有人问起  你就是我叔叔
I'm Abra Stone. And if anyone asks, you're my uncle.
丹叔叔
Uncle Dan.
这也不是撒谎  不完全是
And that's not even a lie. Not totally.
我们在别的方面也算有关系
We're related in other ways.
你像我一样有魔法
You're magic, like me.
我不了解魔法
I don't know about magic.
我...
I...
我一直管它叫闪灵
I always called it the shining.
是的  我们都有闪灵能力
And, yeah, we both shine.
你父母知道吗
Do your parents know?
我的闪灵能力
About my shine?
他们害怕
They're scared of it,
但他们以为能力消失了  除了几件事
but they think it's gone except for a few things.
比如我妈妈有时会让我帮她
Like, my mom sometimes asks me to help her
找她弄丢的东西
find something she's lost.
上个月  是她的车钥匙
Last month, it was her car keys.
她落在了车库里我爸爸的工作台上
She left them on my dad's worktable in the garage.
但他们避而不谈
But they don't talk about it.
如果我使用能力  他们会用异样的眼神看我
Or if I use it, they look at me different.
或者完全不看我
Or not at all.
有一次一整天都没看我
Not for a whole day once.
不肯直视我的眼睛
Wouldn't look me in the eyes.
所以我尽力不去使用
So, I try not to use it.
因为如果别人发现了
Because if people find out,
会认为我是个怪胎  知道吧
"Eek, a freak." You know?
你肯定知道
Sure you know.
你也尽力不去使用
You try not to use it, too.
你已经坚持很久了
You've been trying a long time,
她也不肯直视你的眼睛
and she couldn't look you in your eyes either.
我小时候
When I was a kid,
我不理解闪灵  我叫它"托尼"
I didn't understand the shining. I called it "Tony."
我以为他是我的幻想好友
I thought he was my imaginary friend.
我以为你是我的幻想好友
I thought you were my imaginary friend...
那样想了很久
for a long time.
我们这样的人有多少
How many of us are out there?
很多人都有一点闪灵能力
There's a lot of people who have a little bit of shine,
他们自己都不知道
they don't even know it.
他们总在妻子伤心时
They always seem to come home with flowers
正好带着花回家
when their wives are sad,
或者没有复习就考得很好
or they do well on the school test they didn't study for.
但我一辈子也只认识
But I only met two or three people
两三个知道自己有闪灵能力的人
in my whole life who knew they shined.
棒球男孩有闪灵能力
The baseball boy shined.
他叫布莱德利·特雷弗
His name was Bradley Trevor.
这些人
These people...
他们看起来都不像人  抓走了他
they look like people anyway, they took him.
他们吃了他
And they ate him.
他们吃了他的闪灵
They ate his shine.
你可以感觉到吗
You could feel it?
我觉得他们能感觉到我
And they could feel me, I think.
至少其中一位能  一位女士
At least one of them did. A lady.
戴帽子的女士
The lady with the hat.
我想找到他们  阻止他们
I wanna find them, stop them,
因为我觉得他们杀害过其他很多孩子
because I think they've done this to a lot of other kids, too.
所以我得做些什么  对吧
So, I have to do something, right?
你为什么要来这里
Why did you come here?
为什么是我
Why me?
因为你能听到我的声音
Because you can hear me.
你会相信我  你也有闪灵能力
You'd believe me. You shine, too.
他们伤害我们这样的人
And they hurt people like us.
你会怎么做
I mean, what would you do?
如果你能拿到他身上的东西
If you could get something of his,
如果你能去爱荷华
if you could go to Iowa...
-等等  -我可以帮你找到他
- Whoa, hang on. - I can help you find him.
那样他的父母就能知道他的下落
Then his parents would know where he was.
至少可以好好埋葬他
They could bury him right, at least.
我们还可以拿到他的手套
We could also get his glove.
如果我能碰到手套  就可以追踪他们
If I can touch that glove, I can track them.
等等  等等
Easy. Easy.
因为大块头巴里  那人好像叫这个名字
Because Barry the Chunk, I think that was his name,
他们杀死他之前的一段时间
for a while, before they killed him,
那人戴过他的手套
he was wearing it.
阿布拉  回家去
Abra, go home.
想想你的学业  想想你的父母
Think about your school. Think about your parents.
想想你的余生
Think about the rest of your life.
别追踪这些人
Don't chase these people.
别激怒他们
Don't aggravate them.
无论如何  都不要吸引他们的注意力
And whatever you do, don't attract their attention.
别使用闪灵能力
Don't shine.
想想办法  任何办法
Find something, anything...
差不多是任何办法吧  阻止你的闪灵
Well, almost anything, to stop that shine of yours.
低调行事  掩藏你的闪灵  祈求上帝
Keep your head down, keep your shine down and hope to God
让那些人  或者类似的生物
that these people or anything like them,
不会发现你
that they don't see you.
如果他们发现了你  他们会回来
If they see you, they come back.
阿布拉  你明白吗
Abra, do you hear me?
他们会回来
They come back.
低调行事  注意安全
Keep your head down. Stay safe.
对不起
I'm sorry.
那年很不容易
Things were tough that year.
很多演员都失业了
A lot of actors were out of work.
大家好
Hey, fellas.
杂耍大明星埃尔默·福德来了
Here comes Elmer Fudd that big vaudeville star.
怎么了
What is it?
没事  医生
Oh, it's nothing, Doc.
没事
It's nothing.
想起爸爸了
Thinking about Dad.
我没有
No, I'm not.
你有  而且你不愿想起
You are. And you don't want to.
别担心我  医生
Don't worry about me, Doc.
我没事
I'm fine.
我们都没事
We're fine.
阿兹
Hey, Azzie.
你今晚搞错了吧
You got your wires crossed tonight.
那是个空房间  阿兹
That room's empty, Az.
那房间里没人
There's no one in that room.
等等  医生
Whoa! Hang on, Doc.
迪克
Dick.
我很抱歉
Oh, I'm so sorry.
我...我还以为是...
I... I... I thought it was...
以为我是眺望酒店里那些东西
Thought I was from the Overlook.
差点把我锁起来
Almost locked me up.
那些老鬼魂还来找你吗
Still getting visits from them old ghosts?
没有  好几年都没来了
No, not for years.
霍勒斯·德文特是最后一位
Horace Derwent was the last one,
他的西装上都是五彩纸屑
confetti on his suit.
和我说  "派对很棒吧"
Said, "Great party, isn't it?"
脸上挂着欠揍的笑容  直到我把他关进盒子
Shit-eating grin on his face till I pulled out a box for him.
他的笑容消失得很快
That grin went fast.
我过去一直都没想到要问你
Hey, it never occurred to me to ask you back then.
把他们关进盒子后会怎么样
What happens to them in those boxes?
他们会死在里面吗
Do they die in there?
你在乎吗
Do you care?
我想你了
I missed you.
已经很久没见了吗
Has it been a long time?
我分不清
Can't tell.
这个世界现在对我来说是一个梦中梦
This world is a dream of a dream to me now.
八年多一点
Eight years. Little more.
上次我见你时
Last time I saw you,
你陷入了低谷
you was at the bottom.
现在看起来好多了
You look better now.
你为什么来这里
Why are you here?
我来这里是因为一切都是轮回
I'm here because it all comes 'round.
灵魂周而复始  医生
Ka's a wheel, Doc.
听好了  孩子
You listen, son.
我来这里很痛苦  所以我只说一次
It hurts to be here, so I'll only say it once.
如果那些空洞的恶魔
These empty devils ever found you
在你小时候找到了你
when you was a tyke,
只要他们嗅到你的一丝气息
if they'd even sniffed you,
你早就死了
you'd be long dead.
他们就像是大地患上的癌症
They're on the land like a cancer on the skin.
他们曾在沙漠里骑骆驼
Once, they rode camels in the desert.
也曾组织车队穿越东欧
Once, they drove caravans across Eastern Europe.
他们以尖叫为食
They eat screams,
以痛苦为饮
and drink pain,
他们已经注意到了那个小女孩
and they've noticed that little girl.
他们可能会杀了她
They might kill her,
可能会转化她
might turn her,
或者养着她  直到她被榨干
or might keep her till she's all used up,
那是最坏的情况
and that'd be worst of all.
你不能让他们得逞
You can't let 'em.
为什么是我
Why me?
因为她找到了你
Because she found you.
因为她出现了  见鬼  医生  为什么是我
Because she showed up. Hell, Doc, why me?
你也有一天突然走进我的厨房
You just walked on into my kitchen one day,
到现在我都解脱不了
and I'm still on the hook.
我到底该怎么做
What the hell am I supposed to do?
她要什么就给她
Get her what she asked for.
你不会再见到我了  医生
You won't see me again, Doc.
这是我最后的梦
This is my last dream.
看来你成长为一个好人了  孩子
It seems to me you grew up fine, son,
但你还欠一笔债
but you still owe a debt.
还清它
Pay it.
见鬼  什么事
God, damn it. What?
抱歉打扰了
Sorry to interrupt.
我告诉过你"不许打扰我"  是不是
I told you, "No distractions." Didn't I?
不吃不喝
Nothing to eat, nothing to drink.
安宁平静地冥想
Just peace, quiet, and meditation.
我今晚要集中精力对付她  乌鸦
I need all my wits for her tonight, Crow.
所以我才要来  我有发现
That's why I'm here. I found something.
安尼斯顿发生小型地震
最微弱的地震能有多微弱
"How small can an earthquake be?
安尼斯顿的里奇兰街在索科河中断
Pretty small, if the people of Richland Court,
如果那里的居民可信
a short Anniston street that
那么地震可以非常微弱
dead-ends at the Saco River, are to be believed.
周二深夜
Late Tuesday night,
这条街上几名居民称有地震
several residents of the street reported a tremor
致使窗户作响  地板摇晃
that rattled windows, shook floors,
架子上的玻璃器具滚落
and sent glassware tumbling from the shelves.
尽管伦瑟姆的地质监测中心
Although the Geological Survey Center in Wrentham
报告上周二新英格兰地区没有地震"
reports there were no temblors in New England last Tuesday."
你怎么想
What do you think?
我想  也许吧
I think, maybe.
不能百分百确定  但有五成可能也不错
I'm not a hundred percent, but I'll take fifty-fifty.
如果那真的是她
If that's actually her...
里奇兰街
Richland Court.
真的是她摇动了新罕布什尔的整条街
She did that, shook a whole street in New Hampshire...
有一个可以集中调查的地方
Having a place to actually focus on,
不是一个城镇  而是一条街
not just a town, but a street,
会让我今晚容易得多
is gonna make things a hell of a lot easier for me tonight.
查得好
Good catch.
你要怎么对付她
How you coming at her?
到时候她睡着了
Well, she'll be asleep.
我探查一下  看看是不是她
I'll just wanna look around, see if she is.
植入一些暗示  如同小虫子
Plant some suggestions, like little worms.
让它们挖掘
Let them burrow.
一百条关于她亲爱的朋友  真结族的虫子
A hundred worms about her dear friends, the Knot.
等我们出现
And when we roll up,
她会高兴得迫不及待跳上车
she'll be so happy to see us, she'll just hop right in the van.
如果这是她干的
If she did this...
她真的摇动了整条街
really shook a whole street,
你应该小心点
I think you should be careful.
她只是个小女孩
She's a little girl.
而你永远是最凶悍的女王
And you are the queen bitch of all time.
我知道
I know.
就是说说
Just saying.
小心点
Be careful.
妈妈
Mom.
你感觉还好吗
You feeling okay?
你没下来吃晚饭
We missed you at dinner.
我挺好  只是今天过得不顺
I'm okay. Just had a rough day.
我明早要坐飞机去看奶奶
I'm flying out to see momo in the morning.
我会尽早回来
I'll be back as soon as I can.
阿布  她...
Abs, is she...
她这次能挺过去吗
Is she gonna pull through this time?
我不知道
I don't know.
我希望能
I hope so.
告诉她我爱她
Tell her I love her.
接着睡  公主
Keep sleeping, princess.
你们这些凡人
You rubes.
一辈子都在做小盒子
Spend your whole lives making little boxes,
渺小的记忆
little memories.
你们以为这样就无比充实了
Oh, you think they make you so rich.
你真该看看我的  孩子
You should see mine, kiddo.
我的脑子就像个大教堂
Oh, my mind's a cathedral.
你好啊
Well, hi there.
他说你会回来的
He said you'd come back.
你的确回来了
And you did.
很好
Good.
不
No!
退后  退后
Get back! Get back!
你只是个小孩
You're just a fucking child!
你在哪里
Where are you?
哪里  你在哪里  哪里
Where? Where did you...? Where...?
你在哪里  你在哪里
What did you...? Where did you...?
不
No.
出去  出去
Get out! Get out!
出去
Get out!
萝西
Rose?
陷阱
Trap.
发生了什么
What the hell happened?
-那小贱人给我设了个陷阱  -老天  你的手
- Little bitch set a trap for me. - Oh, my God. Your hand.
萝西  萝西  冷静
Rose! Rose, calm down.
我们知道她在哪里了  对吗  我们现在知道了
We know where she is now, right? Now we know.
她刚刚在我脑子里
She was in my head!
-什么  -偷东西
- What? - Stealing!
她知道了什么
What does she know?
我不知道  我不知道
I don't know. I don't know.
-她知道了多少...  -我不知道
- How much does she... - I don't know!
-我不知道  -出了个问题
- I don't know... - There's a problem.
现在不行
Not now!
弗力克大爷
Grampa Flick...
他开始循环了
I think he's cycling.
丹叔叔  丹叔叔  我伤到她了
Uncle Dan! Uncle Dan, I hurt her.
我真的伤到她了
I really hurt her.
我伤到她了  她活该
I hurt her and she deserved it
这还不是最棒的  最棒的是...
and that's not the best part. The best part is...
最棒的是我进入了她的脑子  我进入了她的脑子
The best part is I got in her head. I got in her head.
-丹叔叔  你听到了吗  -天呐  阿布拉
- Uncle Dan? Are you there? - Oh, God, Abra.
你能听到吗
Can you hear me?
你做了什么
What have you done?
跟那孩子聊聊吧
Just talk to the kid.
如果我们要做的话  那就豁出去了
If we're gonna do this, then let's do this.
你好  阿布拉
Hi, Abra.
我听得到
I can hear you.
我不明白
I don't understand.
你会明白的
You will.
我以为我们永生不死
I thought we lived forever.
有人跟你这么保证过吗  安蒂
Did someone promise you that, Andi?
有人说过你不朽不灭吗
Did someone say you're immortal?
我说的是"长生不老  吃得好"
I said, "Live long, eat well."
我们能活得很久  非常久
We can live long, very long.
我们的确如此
And we do,
绝大多数如此
most of us.
但我们吃得不好
But we haven't been eating well.
很长时间了
Not for a long time.
萝西  他不行了
Rosie, he's going.
萝西
Rosie.
怎么  亲爱的
Yes, love?
我害怕
I'm scared.
不  你不害怕
No, you're not.
你目睹过王朝的兴衰
You watched empires rise and fall.
在罗马为角斗士喝彩
Cheered the gladiators in Rome.
扬帆大海
Sailed across oceans,
驶向新世界
to new worlds,
你曾猎食国王  王子  教皇
while you fed on kings, and princes, and popes.
人们书写你的传说
They wrote myths of you,
为你塑雕像
and made statues,
他们在村庄里  被窝里
and they trembled in their villages, and beds,
摩天大楼里战栗
and skyscrapers.
所以
So, no...
你不害怕
you're not scared.
你是王
You're a king...
你以恐惧为食
and you eat fear.
兄弟
Hey, bro.
现在是凌晨四点
You know, it's 4:00 a.m.
你和我朝夕相处  比利
You've always seen me, Billy.
你看人很准  这么说对吗
You have a good sense about people, is that fair to say?
对  怎么...
Yeah, what...
你认为我诚实吗  是好人吗
You think I'm an honest man? A good man?
是  是  丹  我...
I do, I do. Dan, I...
我需要你帮忙
I need your help.
首先需要你听我讲个故事
The first thing I need is for you to listen to a story
并且尽你所能去相信我
and try harder than you've ever tried to believe me.
如何
How's it going?
你不是该准备上学了吗
Shouldn't you be getting ready for school?
是  但我想跟着
Yeah, but I wanted to tag along.
你开了多久了
How long have you been driving?
几个小时吧
A few hours or so.
我们今天夜里应该能到
We should get there tonight. Late.
那是谁
Who's that?
他是我朋友
He's my friend.
也许是我最好的朋友
Maybe my best friend.
你应该看看她的脸
You should've seen her face.
她害怕了  丹叔叔
She was scared, Uncle Dan.
就像那些孩子一样害怕
Scared like all those kids were scared.
那些被她杀害的孩子
All those kids she's killed.
我的侵入让她既愤怒又恐惧
She was so mad and so scared that I got in.
那是个新招数
That was a new trick.
我以前从来没那么做过
I've never done that before.
我也没做过  那是什么感觉
Yeah, me neither. What was it like?
像个图书馆
Like a library.
我猜我们内心都是图书馆
I guess we're all libraries inside.
你怎么做的
How'd you do it?
就像这样  轻轻一推
Like this. Just a little push.
阿布拉
Abra!
对不起  对不起  对不起
Sorry! Sorry, sorry, sorry!
-对不起  我不是故意的  -没事
- I'm sorry. I didn't mean to. - It's okay.
那些盒子都是什么
What were all those boxes?
没什么
Nothing.
说谎
Liar.
我小的时候
When I was a kid,
比你还小的时候  我遇到了类似这样的东西
younger than you, I bumped into something like these things
像他们一样吃人的东西
that ate like they do.
只不过那不是人  是个地方
Only it wasn't a person, it was a place.
后来他们封锁了那里  荒废了
They closed it down after and let it rot.
但住在那里的东西  他们...
But the things that lived there, they...
别再去那里乱转了
Don't go poking around in there again.
好  我不去了  我保证
Okay, I won't. I promise.
我们快准备好了  正在装车
We're almost ready. We're just loading up.
好
Good.
开车上路
Get the caravan on the road
我们一两天内就能抓到她
and we'll have her in a day or two.
我觉得你不该去  萝西
I don't think you should come, Rosie.
你他妈说什么
The fuck did you just say?
她瞄上了你
She tagged you.
她进入过你的脑子
She got in your head.
对  那不会再发生了
Yeah, it won't happen again.
谁知道你把她赶出去前她摸清了多少
And who knows how much she got to before you kicked her out.
她是我的  乌鸦
She's mine, Crow.
现在  据我们所知
Right now, as far as we know,
你是我们中她唯一可以追踪的人
you are the only one of us she could track.
如果她看到你要去了
Now, if she sees you coming,
她可能会逃跑
she could run
或者再设一个陷阱
or set another trap.
我会弄晕她
I will knock her out cold.
我们在国家安全局的人给我弄了好货
One of our assets from the NSA gave me the good stuff.
能放倒她  不会有药物过量的风险
Put her out without chance of an overdose.
我往南去  兜一圈
I'll head south. I'll circle around.
从另一个方向袭击她
I'll come at her from a different direction.
我应该去的
I should be there.
你知道我说得对
You know I'm right about this.
行
Okay.
你想要的话  我可以让安蒂留下陪你
I'll leave Andi here with you, if you want.
不  你们需要全部的战力
No, no, you'll need your strength, all of you.
如果她对你们耍花招
If she pulls a trick on you,
待在一起
stay together.
好吗
Yeah?
但我也有自己的招数
But I got some tricks of my own.
我想我们到了
Hey, I think we're here.
好
Okay.
看看能不能联系上她
I'll see if I can get her.
阿布拉
Abra?
拉美克工业
乙醇工厂
东北入口
关停待通知
就是那个标牌  绕去后面
That's the sign. Pull around back.
她说绕去后面
She says to pull around back.
我会告诉你在哪停
And I'll tell you when to stop.
她会告诉我们在哪停
She'll tell us when to stop.
老实说  丹
I gotta tell you, Danno,
我不知道我希望你是对的还是错的
I don't know whether I hope you're right or wrong about this.
如果你是错的  那我朋友疯了
I mean, if you're wrong, my friend is crazy.
彻头彻尾地疯了
I mean, full-blown, mental breakdown,
幻想的怪物杀害幻想的小孩
imaginary-monsters- killing-imaginary-kids
疯了
bonkers.
不过...这我可以接受
But, you know, I... I can work with that.
但如果你是对的...
If you're right, though...
我知道
I know.
那就更糟了
It's much worse.
你应该回家去
You should go home.
什么
What?
不  不是说你
No, not you.
我能应付
I can handle it.
不  接下来就交给我们
No. We'll take it from here.
好  只有我们了
Okay, it's just us.
你闻到了吗
You smell that?
我以前打过猎  跟你说过吗
Used to hunt. I ever tell you that?
没有
No.
猎鹿
Deer.
有个夏天
This one summer,
我打伤了一头公鹿
I clipped this buck.
我追了它两天
I was tracking it for two days.
射中了  打伤了它
I got the shot, clipped him.
它跑了  我去追
He ran off, I went after.
以为它不会坚持多久
Figured he wasn't gonna last long.
然后它消失了
Then he vanished.
就那么失去踪影
Just up and evaporated.
毫无痕迹  真的莫名其妙
Not a trace. Truly baffling.
五天后
Five days later,
我在另一个地方打猎  隔了好几公里
I'm trying a different spot, miles away.
我在那里找掩蔽的地方
I come around looking for a spot for a blind...
然后我闻到了它
then I smelled him.
闻到了它
Smelled him.
找到了那头公鹿
Found that buck
躲在一个中空的树干里
holed up to a hollow trunk,
死了好几天
dead for days.
那气味...
The smell...
从那以后我再不打猎
Never hunted a day since.
这是同样的气味
This is the same smell.
比利
Billy.
老天
Oh, my God!
操
Fuck.
操  丹  什么鬼
Fuck, Danno. What the fuck?
他们甚至没有好好埋葬他  埋得很浅
They didn't even bury him deep. They buried him shallow.
抱歉  比利
I'm sorry, Billy.
你把我们卷入什么事里了
What did you get us into?
第五章
小戏法
杀害他的那些人
The people who did that...
他们不是人
They're not people.
不  他们不是
No. No, they ain't.
会这样伤害一个小男孩的人
Anyone do that to a little boy,
都不是人
they ain't people.
你们找到了吗
Did you get it?
找到了
Yeah, we got it.
她回来了吗
Is she back?
我们正在往你那里赶  早上就到
We're heading back to you. We'll be back in the morning.
我们中途要停一下
We got a stop to make.
我需要你给你父母看看发生的事
I need you to show your parents what's happening.
不要
No.
-要的  -不  他们几乎以为我正常了
- Yeah. - No. They almost think I'm normal.
如果我告诉他们  他们会...
If I tell them, they'll...
萝西会通过他们对付你
Rose'll go through them to get to you.
你知道的  不是吗
You know that, don't you?
她会毫不迟疑杀死他们
She'll cut them down without a second thought.
而她要来了  阿布拉
And she's coming, Abra.
他们需要知道
They need to know.
我们要在哪里停一下
So, what's this stop we gotta make?
你还留着猎鹿的步枪吗
You still got those old deer rifles?
你是丹叔叔吗
You're Uncle Dan?
-你以为你是谁  -先生
- The fuck you think you are? - Sir...
她才十三岁
She is 13 years old!
阿布拉  我告诉过你要给他看看
Abra, I told you to show him.
-我告诉他了  -那不一样
- I told him. - Well, that's not the same.
我要痛揍你一顿  然后报警
I'm gonna kick your ass before I call the police, huh?
不不不  阿布拉
No, no, no. Abra.
别叫她的名字
Now, don't you say her name.
阿布拉
Abra...
对不起  斯通先生  我是你们的朋友
I'm sorry, Mr. Stone. I am a friend.
她告诉你的事都是真的
Everything she told you is true.
到底发生了什么
What the hell is happening?
对不起
I'm sorry.
阿布拉需要给你看点东西
Abra needs to show you something.
我看到了那个男孩
I saw the boy.
我看到了他的尸体
I saw his body.
都是真的
It's all true.
很可能是你这个朋友把他埋在那里的
Probably, your friend here put him there.
你想过吗
You think about that?
没想太久
Not for long, I didn't.
斯通先生  你的女儿很特别
Mr. Stone, your daughter is special.
不准谈论她
Don't talk about her.
我想你内心深处知道
I think you know that. Deep down.
她知道那个小男孩出了什么事
She knows what happened to that little boy,
她还知道是谁干的
and she knows who did it.
给他看看
Show him.
对不起  爸爸
I'm sorry, Daddy.
我真的不想
I really didn't want to.
不想做什么
Didn't want to what?
不用  谢谢
No, thanks.
不用
No.
那些人
Those people...
他们知道我女儿的能力吗
they know about my daughter?
知道
They do.
而且他们迟早会来
And sooner or later, they're coming.
我们必须做点什么
We gotta do something.
我们报警  找联调局
All right, we're calling the police, the FBI...
那些人已经活了很久很久  先生
These people have been around a long, long time, sir.
他们有钱  有关系
They're rich, connected.
我觉得他们根本不怕警察
I don't think they're worried about the police.
但他们在哪
But where are they?
他们什么时候来  我们能去哪
When are they coming? Where can we go?
阿布拉能回答这些
Abra can answer that...
只要她准备好了
if she's ready.
我准备好了
I'm ready.
你确定想这么做吗
You sure you wanna do this?
我必须做
I have to.
I95公路
I-95.
巴里  乌鸦  蛇  还有别的几个
Barry, the Crow, the Snake, and a few others.
树木看起来没什么不同
The trees haven't changed that much,
所以或许在马萨诸塞
so maybe Massachusetts,
-不过他们很近了  -萝西呢
- but they're close. - Rose?
没看到她
Didn't see her.
但他们要来了
But they're coming.
这是她唯一看到的房间吗
This is the only room she saw?
是的
That's right.
我做了些改变  藏了几样东西
And I made a few changes. Hid a few things.
好的
All right.
他们会试图追踪你
Well, they'll be trying to track you,
试图搞明白
trying to catch on.
而你要让他们得逞
And you're gonna let them.
你疯了吗
Are you crazy?
可能吧  但你要让他们得逞
Possibly, but you're gonna let them.
然后我需要你变个戏法
And then I need you to try and do a little trick.
变魔法吗
A magic trick?
他们在跟踪我们
They're following us.
集中注意  你得坚持到他们到达
Concentrate. You gotta keep it up until they land.
我知道
I know.
这里应该可以
This should work.
那边和那边都有遮蔽
Good blinds over there, and there.
他们还在附近吗
They still close?
应该越来越近了
Getting closer, I think.
很难坚持
This is tough.
我知道  不用多久了
I know. I know. Not much longer.
好了  乌鸦老爹
Okay, Crow Daddy,
去抓她吧
go get her.
你看起来挺放松
You look relaxed.
你感觉放松  是吧  阿布拉
You feel relaxed, don't you, Abra?
可能吧
I guess.
你应该这样
You should.
放松
Just relax.
我们是朋友
We're friends.
你们是朋友
You're friends.
没错
That's right.
只是朋友
Just friends.
我们想带你见更多朋友
And we want to take you to meet more friends.
好朋友
Good friends.
靠
Well, shit.
他们把你说得那么厉害
The way they talked you up,
我还以为不会这么轻易抓到你呢
I was thinking it'd be a little harder than that.
搞什么
The fuck?
小戏法  只是该死的小戏法
Parlor tricks. Just fuckin' parlor tricks.
不  离开那里
No! Get out of there!
离开那里
Get out of there!
不
No!
你们活该
You deserve it.
你们所有人都活该
You deserve it. All of you.
不
No!
该死
Fuck.
停下
Stop.
我只有一个问题问你  亲爱的
I just got one question for you, sweetie.
你不想睡吗
Aren't you sleepy?
你想睡了
You're sleepy.
睡吧
Sleep.
醒醒  丹叔叔
Wake up! Uncle Dan!
醒醒  醒醒
Wake up! Wake up.
醒醒
Wake up!
该死的男人
Fucking men.
别过来  比利
Stay back, Billy.
自杀吧
Kill yourself.
不
No!
比利
Billy!
少了一个
There is one missing.
我没看到乌鸦  乌鸦在哪
I didn't see the Crow. Where is the Crow?
你好  阿布拉
Hello, Abra.
阿布拉
Abra!
离她远点
Get away from her.
退后
Step back.
没问题  爸爸
Sure thing, Dad.
我很高兴能见到你
You know, I'm glad I got to meet you.
我要杀了你  退后
I'll fucking kill you. Step back.
真敢说
Some brave words.
看你们这些凡人威胁神总让我发笑
Always tickles me, watching you rubes threaten a god.
知道吗  你的女儿
You know, your little girl,
或许会成为我们吃过最好的食物
she's maybe the best food we'll ever have.
很高兴能有机会向大厨致意
I'm so glad I had a chance to compliment the chef.
很好  你醒了
Good, you're awake.
丹
Dan...
别费劲了
Don't bother.
我是怎么了
What's wrong with me?
你被下药了  小姐
You've been dosed, missy.
我从没用过这么大的剂量
More than I've ever used before.
你可能时不时会醒过来
Might let you wake up here and there,
但你的灵气睡得很沉
but that steam of yours is fast asleep.
我爸爸
My dad...
我爸爸怎么了
What happened to my dad?
今天很多好人被杀了
Lot of good people killed today.
很多好人
Lot of good people.
我也想告诉你会有人付出代价
I'd love to tell you someone will pay,
会有某种正义降临为今天的悲剧做主
some kind of justice raining down on the sad events today,
但事实并非如此
but it don't work like that.
我们总是会抓到你的
We were always gonna have you.
我们一些人死了
Some of my people are dead.
你们一些人死了
Some of yours are dead.
不过结果没变
Outcome didn't change, though.
想一下
Think on that a minute.
结果没变
The outcome didn't change.
所以他们的死
So, their deaths,
他们所有人
all of them,
都是白死
just a waste.
都是因为你的所作所为  小姑娘
A waste you brought on to us all, young lady.
为了什么
For what?
请听到我的声音
Please hear me...
不会有人听到
Ain't nobody hearing you.
不如冷静下来  享受旅行
Might as well calm down and enjoy the ride.
就像我说的
Like I said,
结果没变
outcome hasn't changed.
不
No.
拜托
Please.
拜托  拜托  拜托
Oh, please, please, please.
拜托
Please.
阿布拉
Abra!
Abra.
托尼
Tony?
求你帮帮我  托尼
Help me, please, Tony.
天啊
God.
好  好  好
Okay. Okay. Okay, okay.
好了  你总是说
Okay, you always said...
你的大脑就像无线电
your brain was like a radio.
呼叫的时候没人回应  就不要呼叫了
No one's answering when you call, so stop calling.
听就可以
And just listen.
丹  丹
Dan. Dan.
救我
Help.
谋杀
谁
棒球男孩
希望你没事
你的朋友  丹
丹
Dan.
他给你下药了吗
Did he drug you?
抱歉
I'm so sorry.
我试试别的办法  好吗
I'm gonna try something, okay?
但你很虚弱
But you're weak.
他在阻隔你
He's blocking you.
我几乎听不见你说话
I could barely hear you.
你得相信我  好吗
You gotta trust me, okay?
好吗
Okay?
又醒了吗
Awake again, huh?
可能得在下个休息区给你下药
Might have to dose you at the next rest stop.
我们要去哪里
Where are we going?
你心里很清楚
You know where.
操  我感觉就像宿醉
Fuck, I feel hungover.
我告诉过你那是好货
I told you it's good shit.
好几年没宿醉了  我并不想念这种感觉
Haven't felt hungover in years. And, you know, I don't miss it.
一点都不
Not even a little.
往西走吗
West, huh?
远离主路  很明智
Stayin' off the major roads. Smart.
克朗威尔  纽约
Crownville. New York.
你是谁
Who are you?
我就是杀了你朋友的人
I'm the guy that killed your friends.
很高兴认识你
It's nice to meet you.
戏法不错
Neat trick.
之间没见过这样的
Haven't seen this one before.
想再看一个吗
Wanna see one more?
你要是对我开枪  萝西应该不会开心
Don't imagine Rose'll be too happy if you shoot the prize.
出这些事萝西应该一点都不开心
I don't suppose Rose will be happy about any of this.
那个女人要是生气了
And when that woman gets mad...
我觉得你知道得够多了
Well, it seems to me you know enough
清楚你就不该管这事
to know you might wanna sit this one out.
你应该知足
Count your blessings.
过你自己的生活
Go on your way.
什么事这么好笑
What's so funny, friend?
就是傲慢  真的就是傲慢
Well, it's just arrogance. It's arrogance, really.
不过如果觉得自己可以永生  倒也说得通
But it makes sense, if you think you're gonna live forever.
所以很显然  你不会想着系安全带
Stands to reason, of course you wouldn't wear your seatbelt.
不
No!
丹
Dan?
但愿你感到很痛
I hope that hurts.
萝西
Rosie...
非常痛
A lot.
你个小婊子
You little bitch.
你都干了什么
What have you done?
好啊  小婊子
All right, bitch child.
好啊
All right.
抱歉
Sorry.
睡过去了
Dozed off.
没事  你该睡会儿
No, you earned it.
我们在哪里
Where are we?
俄亥俄
Ohio.
我们要去哪里
Where are we going?
科罗拉多
Colorado.
为什么是科罗拉多
Why Colorado?
她还会来的
She's gonna keep coming.
-我知道  -不会停下
- I know. - Always.
只有解决了她才会结束
This only ends if we end it,
但我觉得我们打不过她
and I don't think we can beat her.
光靠我们两个不行
Not by ourselves.
有一个地方
There's a place.
一个对我们这样的人来说很危险的地方
A place that's dangerous for people like us.
就是你说过的那个饥饿的地方吗
The place you told me about? The hungry place?
对  没错
Yeah, that's right.
如果那么危险  我们为什么还要去
If it's so dangerous, why would we go there?
如果对我们来说很危险
Well, if it's dangerous for people like us,
我想对她来说也会很危险
I expect it's dangerous for people like her.
可能对她更危险
Maybe even more so.
好
Good.
她在跟踪我们
She's following us, you know.
很好  让她跟着吧
Yeah, good. Let her.
你爸爸的事我很遗憾
I'm sorry about your father.
你朋友的事我也很遗憾
Sorry about your friend.
是我妈妈
It's my mom.
我要怎么跟她说
What do I say to her?
妈妈
Hi, Mom.
谢天谢地
Thank God!
阿布拉
Abra...
你还好吗  你在哪里
Are you okay? Where are you?
我爱你
I love you.
等我们安全了  你会告诉她去哪找我们吧
When we're safe, you'll call her and tell her where to find us?
我会的
I will.
好
Okay.
没有多远了  就在山上
Not too much further. Up the mountain.
第六章
遗忘之物
我们这么办
Here's what we're gonna do.
你待在车里  一直开着暖气
You're gonna stay in the car, keep the heater running.
除非万不得已
I don't want you spending a minute
我不想让你在里面待哪怕一分钟
inside there if you don't have to.
她只能从这里过来
She can only come from here.
隔着一公里多你就能看见她
You can see her a mile out, easy.
你要是看见那边山上有灯光
You see lights on the mountain over there,
就告诉我  好吗
you blast me, okay?
我不想让你进去  除非她来了
But I don't want you going in. Not until she's here.
你不和我一起等吗
You aren't waiting with me?
不行
I can't.
为什么
Why not?
我得把它弄醒
I have to wake it up.
醒醒
Wakey-wakey.
危险  高压电
红朗姆
今晚有些无聊  托伦斯先生
Slow night, Mr. Torrance.
很快就不会无聊了
Not for long, I imagine.
你喜欢威士忌  对吧
You're a whiskey man, are you not?
以前大多数时候都喜欢
I was, most of the time.
免费赠送
On the house.
这是你喜欢的牌子
This was your brand.
杰克·丹尼尔
Jack Daniel's.
我以前在家里看过这酒瓶
I used to see the bottles in our home.
我们在此之前真正的家
Our real home, before all this.
有次我闻了一下  感觉像是什么烧着了
I smelled one once. It smelled like something on fire,
我想我的感觉没错
which I suppose it was.
恐怕你是把我跟别人搞混了
I'm afraid you've confused me with someone else.
我叫劳伊德
It's Lloyd.
劳伊德
Lloyd.
抱歉  托伦斯先生
I apologize, Mr. Torrance.
我不知道大家都去哪里了  但是会热闹起来的
I don't know where everyone is, but it'll pick up.
我知道他们在哪里
Oh, I know where they are.
你说得没错
And you're right...
会热闹起来的
it'll pick up.
希望你不介意  托伦斯先生  你似乎
If you don't mind my saying, Mr. Torrance, you seem...
被利用了
put upon.
Put upon?
不是这样吗
Ain't that the way.
男人过着自己的生活
Man just living his life,
努力做好自己的工作
trying to do his work.
结果被利用了
He gets put upon.
牵扯进别人的麻烦
Pulled into other people's problems.
我见得太多了  请别介意我这么说
I see it all the time, if you don't mind my saying.
后来我们住在佛罗里达
So we lived in Florida.
你说什么
I'm sorry?
我和妈妈
Mom and I.
恐怕我不知道你说的是谁
I'm afraid I don't know who you mean.
我们再也不想看见雪
We never wanted to see snow again,
所以我们住在佛罗里达
so we lived in Florida.
房子很小  但很舒适  我们很幸福
Tiny place, but it was comfortable, and we were happy.
我们也很悲伤
I mean, we were grieving.
我们受到了精神创伤
We were traumatized,
但同时也有快乐幸福
but there was happiness too.
她
She...
她会移开目光
She would look away.
她看着我
She'd look at me,
但一两秒后总会移开目光
but she'd always look away after a second or two.
过了段时间我才注意到
It took me a while to notice it.
但在眺望酒店之后  她不会直视我的眼睛
But after the Overlook, she wouldn't look me in the eyes,
不会一直看着
not for long.
我一直不理解
Couldn't figure it out.
但其实
But it...
其实是你
It was you.
她在我眼中看见你  就不得不移开目光
She saw your eyes in me, and she'd have to look away.
这让她备受折磨
It tortured her to have to do that.
所以我治好了
So, I fixed it.
我帮她治好了  那是我最后一次用它
I fixed it for her, and it was the last time I ever used it.
这样她就不会再在我眼中看到你
So that she wouldn't see you anymore when she looked at me.
她去世的时候我二十岁
I was 20 when she died.
那时候我能看出来有人要死了
And back then, I saw when someone was gonna die.
我能看见苍蝇  黑苍蝇
I saw flies. Black flies.
我称之为"死蝇"  它们会绕着人脸飞
"Death flies," I called them, circling people's faces.
最后那几周  她满脸...
And in those last weeks, she was covered...
满脸都是苍蝇
Her whole face.
我几乎看不见她的眼睛
I could barely see her eyes.
我试着安慰她  但是我几乎没法直视她
And I... I tried to comfort her, but I could hardly look at her.
她看出来了
And she saw that.
她就躺在那里奄奄一息
She just lay there dying,
而她的儿子都没法直视她
with her son who couldn't look at her.
或许喝点烈的来忘掉那种不快
Maybe something warm to push away such unpleasantries.
你不想听听吗  她是你妻子
Don't you wanna hear about it? She was your wife.
我觉得你可能把我当成了别人
I think you've mistaken me for someone else.
-我只是个酒保  -是吗
- I'm just a bartender. - Oh, yeah?
只是酒保劳伊德  在眺望酒店倒倒酒
Just Lloyd the bartender, pouring joy at the Overlook Hotel.
你想喝什么我都给你  托伦斯先生
I'll pour whatever you like, Mr. Torrance.
爸
Oh, Dad.
这杯酒代价必然不菲
This drink will cost an awful lot.
你的钱在这里没用
Your money is no good here.
免费赠送
Orders from the house.
它的代价不在于金钱
It'll cost more than money.
它会毁掉我的八年努力
It'll cost me eight years.
过去的八年  谁知道我未来还有几年
Eight behind me, and who knows how many in front of me.
你的信用没问题  托伦斯先生
Your credit is fine, Mr. Torrance.
君唤一壶酒
Man takes a drink,
千杯入愁肠
the drink takes a drink,
酒销人已亡
and then the drink takes a man.
不是这样吗  爸
Ain't it so, Dad?
药
Medicine.
它就是药
Medicine is what it is.
真正的灵丹妙药
Bona fide cure-all.
抑郁  压力  悔恨  失败  一扫而光
Depression, stress, remorse, failure, wipes it all away.
思想就是一块黑板
The mind is a blackboard.
而这个
And this
就是黑板擦
is the eraser.
男人努力工作
A man tries.
养家糊口
He provides.
但他周围都是张大的嘴
But he's surrounded by mouths.
吃饭  尖叫  哭喊  唠叨
that eat, and scream, and cry, and nag.
所以他只为自己求一样东西
So, he asks for one thing, just one thing for him.
暖暖身子
To warm him up...
逃离被那些嘴支配的痛苦
to take the sting out of those days of the mouths,
它们不停地吃  吃掉他制造的一切
eating, and eating, and eating everything he makes,
他拥有的一切
everything he has.
还有家庭
And a family.
妻子和孩子
A wife, a kid.
那些嘴吃掉时间
Those mouths eat time.
吃掉你在人间的时日
They eat your days on Earth.
它们狼吞虎咽
They just gobble them up.
足以让一个男人崩溃
It's enough to make a man sick.
而这个
And this...
就是良药
is the medicine.
告诉我  小子
So, tell me, pup,
你要吃药吗
are you gonna take your medicine?
我不要
I'm not.
真不好意思  我很抱歉
Look at that. I'm sorry.
我这老家伙笨手笨脚的  请原谅  托伦斯先生
Clumsy old me, Mr. Torrance. Forgive me.
让我帮你擦干净吧
Let's get you cleaned up.
上头很担心
Management is concerned.
担心
Concerned?
她对你做的事太糟糕了
It's horrible what she's done to you.
把你卷进她的麻烦
Pulled you into her mess.
聪明人会怎么做呢
A smart man?
会让她自己解决
He'd let her handle it.
让事情按本该的样子发展
Let things unfold as they're meant to.
凭什么要你为他买单呢  医生
Why should you pay her tab, Doc?
为了什么呢
And for what?
就为了这个惹来所有麻烦的小姑娘吗
For this little girl who started all this trouble?
那上头想让我怎么做
What would management have me do about that?
什么都不做
Nothing.
这是世间最容易的事情  孩子
Easiest thing in the world to do, son.
把她带进来
Just bring her inside.
然后
And then, well,
接受自己无法改变的事情
you accept the things you cannot change.
丹
Dan!
她来了
She's here.
好
Okay.
这地方病了
This place is sick.
就像我奶奶一样
Sick like my momo was sick.
她得了癌症
It's cancer,
但这地方比那还糟
only worse.
我们现在做什么
What do we do now?
我们进去  她会来找我们
We head inside. She'll find us.
快瞧瞧
Well, well, well.
你们好啊
Hi there.
一旦开始  你就赶快跑
When this starts, run.
没错  你跑吧  亲爱的
Yes, you run, dear.
然后我会找到你
And then I will find you
我会让你尖叫许多年再死去
and you will scream for years until you die.
倒要瞧瞧谁是尖叫的那一个
We'll see who does the screaming.
没错  我们走着瞧
Oh, we'll see indeed.
她说的没错
She's right, you know.
你应该感到害怕
You should be afraid.
为什么
Why is that?
因为你不知道你身处何处
Because you don't know where you're standing.
抱歉  帅哥  你是哪位
I'm sorry, who are you, handsome?
就是你是杀了我的乌鸦  对吧
You're the one who killed my Crow, aren't you?
开始
Go.
真聪明
Clever.
你做了不少改进是吧
You've made some improvements, haven't you?
自从我上次侵入你的脑子之后
Since the last time I was in your mind.
你怎知道不是我们侵入了你的脑子
How do you know we're not in yours?
你在哪呢  小家伙
Where are you, pup?
你将死在这里
You're gonna die here.
真敢说  亲爱的
Brave words, dear.
你真的是那么想的吗
Is that what you really think?
你能伤到我
You're gonna hurt me?
没错
Yes.
你让我想起了我自己
You know, you remind me of myself.
我现在看明白了
I can really see it now.
你内心深藏着黑暗  亲爱的
You've got a darkness in you, dear.
我想你我之间唯一的区别  就是时间
I think the only difference between you and me is time.
你还不知道
You don't know yet...
为了拥有更多的时间
what you'd do...
人都会做些什么
for more time.
不过我跟你保证  亲爱的  你会感到惊讶的
But I promise you, dear, oh, you'd be surprised.
疼痛净化灵气
Pain purifies steam.
恐惧亦然  请你理解
Fear, too, so, you understand.
我年轻时和你一模一样
I was just like you when I was younger.
我非常特别
I was special
也孤身一人
and alone.
但我遇到了给予我归属和使命的人
But I met someone who gave me the gift of purpose, of community.
如果事情不是发展至此
And I might have given you such a gift
我本来也可能给予你同样的馈赠
if things would have gone differently.
不要吗
No?
你很目中无人  是吧
Defiant, aren't you?
和我真像
So much like me.
你的脑子如此...
Your mind is so...
这不是你的脑子  对吗
This isn't your mind, is it?
这根本不是你
This isn't you at all.
你只是个诱饵
You're just the bait.
够了
Enough!
快跑
Run.
我们怎么会没发现你
How the hell did we miss you?
你我本该多年前就相识
You and I should have met years ago.
丹尼
Danny.
那是你的名字  对吧
That's your name, isn't it?
当凡人变老  灵气会发生一些变化
Well, something happens to the steam when you rubes get older.
会被污染
It gets polluted.
变得肮脏
Dirty.
你知道的
You know that.
我能看见你浑身的污秽
I see the grease all over you.
你的闪灵和以前不太一样了
You don't shine quite the same.
成长糟蹋了你的闪灵
Growing up spoils that, I guess.
说真的  帅哥
Seriously, handsome,
你这么多年都躲在哪里
where have you been hiding?
我给你开个条件
I can make you an offer.
一个我绝少开的条件
An offer I rarely make.
是吗  我真期待呢
Oh, yeah? I can't wait.
如此天赋异禀的男孩
Such a gifted boy
长久以来深藏不露
hiding his light under a bushel for so long.
你可以活得很久  也可以活得很好
You could live a long, long time. Live well, too.
尽情放纵  无需承担后果
Indulge yourself, no consequences,
也不会宿醉
no hangovers.
吃得好  长生不老
Eat well, live long.
只剩你一个了  你肯定很孤单
You must be lonely, being the last one.
全世界只剩你一个
I mean, the last one in the world.
亲爱的  我可不是最后一个  差得远呢
Sweetie, I'm not the last. Far from it.
我只不过是最漂亮的一个
I'm just the prettiest.
想必你已经知道我的答复了
I assume you know my answer.
太可惜了
Pity.
那我们还打不打了
So, are we doing this or not?
亲爱的
Oh, sweetie.
瞧瞧
Look at that, huh?
我似乎伤到了你的股动脉
I seem to have nicked your femoral artery there.
你会失血过多而死  是吗
Why, you're gonna bleed to death, huh?
老天  你脾气还真是倔
My, my, what a temper you have.
火气不小
So much fire.
真是浪费
Such a waste!
也许不是浪费
Or maybe not.
见鬼
Oh, damn.
即便在你这个岁数
Even at your age...
还是如此美味
it's so good.
你尝起来就像威士忌
You taste like whiskey.
丹尼
Danny!
小丹尼
Danny boy!
红朗姆
如此深重的恐惧
Oh, so much terror.
你的一生都如此吗
All your life, huh?
太美味了
Delicious.
别伤害我
Don't hurt me!
见鬼
Oh, damn.
什么...不只有你一个
What are... You're not alone in there.
你还藏了什么
What are you hiding, huh?
那些是什么
What's in those?
特别的东西  是吧
Something special, huh?
他们才不特别  他们饿坏了
They're not special. They're starving.
不
No.
No!
你好啊  丹尼
Hello, Danny.
来和我们一起玩
Come and play with us...
永远
forever...
and ever...
永永远远
and ever.
丹叔叔
Uncle Dan.
丹叔叔  搞定了吗
Uncle Dan, is it done?
她死了吗
Is she dead?
派对很棒吧
Great party, isn't it?
阿布拉
Abra!
来啊
Try it.
你在这呢
There you are.
阿布拉
Abra.
你很不乖哦
You've been very, very bad.
你不是丹叔叔
You're not Uncle Dan.
你只是一个面具  一张假的面孔
You're a mask. A false face.
那我能是谁
Who else would I be?
你是这家酒店
You're the hotel.
但他仍然存在
But he's still in there.
那就摘掉面具吧
Mask is off, then.
你为什么笑
Why are you smiling?
因为你不知道你身处何处
Because you don't know where you're standing.
我对这些走廊了如指掌  孩子
I know these halls like my own face, child.
我是说你身处的这具躯体
I mean the body you're standing in.
你戴起的这幅面孔
The face you're wearing.
这是丹·托伦斯  而你并不了解他
That's Dan Torrance, and you don't know him.
丹·托伦斯
Dan Torrance.
丹·托伦斯来到这里做的第一件事
Dan Torrance made one stop as soon as he got here.
就是去了锅炉房
To the boiler room.
你回来了
There you are.
不是让你跑吗
You were supposed to run.
我不想扔下你
I didn't wanna leave you.
我就在我本该在的地方
I'm exactly where I'm supposed to be.
我无法抵抗他们太久  阿布拉  你得赶快离开
I can't hold it off for much longer. Abra, you need to run.
不
No.
没有你我哪也不去
I'm not going anywhere without you.
我得把我们身后的门关上  不是吗
I have to close the door behind us, right?
跑  快跑
Run! Run!
快点  丹叔叔
Come on, Uncle Dan.
快出来
Get out of there.
快点
Come on.
火势扩散地很快
The fire spread fast,
毁掉了酒店
destroying the hotel.
净化了它
Purifying it.
我几乎能听到它的...
I could almost hear it...
尖叫
screaming.
我能听到它在死去
I could hear it dying.
而内心深处  我知道...
And deep inside, I knew...
我知道你没事
I knew you were okay.
抱歉我让你身处险境
I'm sorry I put you in danger.
那是唯一的办法
It was the only way.
我知道
I know.
你认为她说的是真的吗
Do you think she was right
她不是最后一个
when she said she wasn't the last one?
这是个饥肠辘辘的世界
The world's a hungry place.
非常黑暗
A dark place.
也许像他们那样的人还有更多
Maybe there's more of them
或是比他们更可怕的东西
or things like them or worse,
但也有更多像你一样的人
but there are more people like you, too.
挺身而出的人
People who stand.
我第一次见到你时
I told you when I first met you,
就告诉你应该藏起来
I told you that you should hide.
应该低调行事
That you should keep your head down.
掩藏你的闪灵能力
Keep your shine out of sight.
但我错了
But I was wrong.
展现你的闪灵吧  阿布拉·斯通
Shine on, Abra Stone.
尽情展现
You shine on.
晚饭好了
Dinner's ready.
你和谁说话呢
Who are you talking to?
没谁
No one.
我说谎了
That's not true.
我在和丹说话
I was talking to Dan.
我们死后仍然存在
We go on after.
仍然存在
We go on.
他没事
And he's okay.
爸爸也是
So is Daddy.
他真的没事
He really is.
那就好
Good.
来吃饭吗  宝贝
You coming, sweetheart?
马上
In a minute.
♪ Midnight with the stars and you ♪
Midnight, The Stars and You - Ray Noble and His Orchestra
♪ Midnight and a rendezvous ♪
♪ Your eyes held a message tender ♪
♪ Saying "I surrender all my love to you" ♪
♪ Midnight brought us sweet romance ♪
♪ I know all my whole life through ♪
♪ I'll be remembering you ♪
♪ Whatever else I do ♪
♪ Midnight with the stars and you ♪